{
  "arc_name": "Syrup Village",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How does the butler Klahadore adjust his glasses?",
      "answer": "By using his palm to push them up"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did Luffy know Usopp's dad back at Syrup Village?",
      "answer": "Yassop is a member of the Red Hair Pirates"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why was Kuro undercover as a butler for three years?",
      "answer": "To steal Kaya’s wealth without arousing any suspicion"
    },
    {
      "question": "For what occasion did Kaya buy a present for Klahadore?",
      "answer": "His 3-year anniversary of working for her"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first ally to engage the Kuro Pirates after they changed locations?",
      "answer": "Usopp"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did Zoro get out of the oil slick in Syrup Village?",
      "answer": "He used his swords to climb out"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did the Kuro Pirates suddenly get stronger during the fight?",
      "answer": "Jango's hypnotism"
    },
    {
      "question": "Name one of the Nyaban Brothers.",
      "answer": "Buchi and Sham"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do the Symbols on Kuro’s coat represent?",
      "answer": "It’s poop"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why does Kuro adjust his glasses the way he does?",
      "answer": "A habit he picked up from having swords for hands"
    }
  ]
}
